newcondosonline.com 2015-04-02

# New Condos Online | Condos For Sale | Find Condominiums Worldwide | Privacy Policy

#### 1\. Overview

Thank you for visiting www.NewCondosOnline.com (the 'Web Site'), owned and operated by NewCondosOnline, Inc. ("NewCondosOnline"). To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our privacy policy. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use NewCondosOnline's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address. 

#### 2\. Information Collection and Use

The server on which the Web Site is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, and the pages and images requested. 

When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us. 

Our site's newsletter registration form will request that you give us your email address. At a builder's or another sponsor's request, we may assist them with sending out new project information in the form of email to those who register with us at NewCondosOnline.com. You may always opt out of receiving future mailings. 

We use personal information internally to serve our users and to enhance and extend our relationship with our users. For example, by understanding how you use the Sites from your computer, we are able to customize and personalize your experience. More specifically, we use personal information for the purposes for which it was collected (such as to provide you with the services), to anticipate and resolve problems with our Sites, to respond to customer support inquiries, and to send you periodic e-mail newsletters (provided you register to receive our newsletter), and for our own internal operations (including internal analysis as described below). You should review the 'Information Sharing' section to understand when we disclose personal information to third parties. 

To the extent that any of our Sites accessible through the URL www.NewCondosOnline.com have additional or different practices or policies,these practices?will be explained at that Site. 

#### 3\. Children's Issues

The Web Site is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and children under such age must not use the web site or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves. 

#### 4. Information Sharing

We may share information provided by our users in any of the following circumstances: 

  1. At the request of our users 
  2. We provide such information to trusted businesses, real estate agents or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  3. We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of NewCondosOnline, its users or the public. 

If you have registered with us or have an account, we may share the information submitted under your registration or account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We may share your contact information with affiliates and partners in order to aid you in your new home search or to help you find properties specific to the criteria you have provided. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.

We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which NewCondosOnline or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country. 

In the event of a transfer of ownership of NewCondosOnline, Inc., such as by acquisition or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share aggregated information with others. This includes information from which no individuals can be identified. 

#### 5\. Security 

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. In addition, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

#### 6\. Use of Cookies

Our site uses a technology called "cookies," which are small files that are placed on your computer by our servers stored by your browser to help keep track of your user profile. We use cookies to track user trends and improve areas of our sites that our users find valuable. We do not share cookie information with anyone without your permission. 

NewCondosOnline may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

Some advertisers or third party ad servers may also use their own cookies. We do not have access to this information collected by third parties. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our web sites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features of our site, as well as other web sites, will not be available to you. 

#### 7.Use of IP Addresses 

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you're surfing the Web. When you request pages from NewCondosOnline.com, our servers log your IP address. NewCondosOnline collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our Site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you will be anonymous to us. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, or others. 

#### 8\. Links to Third Party Sites 

NewCondosOnline is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may also be linked to websites operated by other companies. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site's respective privacy policies and practices. 

#### 9\. Choice/Opt-Out

Our Sites may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list to not receive future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, it is best to follow the specific instructions outlined within the communication you received from us. However, if you are unable to complete the process indicated in the communications, then just send us an e-mail at [help@newcondosonline.com](mailto:help@newcondosonline.com) with a copy of the undesired email attached to the request and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list. 

#### 10\. Opt-In Content

By signing up to use the facilities of this website, you are agreeing to receive at least one email communication from us regarding listings, or condo information. You do have the option to cancel any further communications from us if you choose to do so.

#### 11\. Contact Information

Questions or comments regarding the Web Site should be sent by e-mail to [help@newcondosonline.com](mailto:help@newcondosonline.com) or by U.S. mail to:

**NewCondosOnline, Inc.**  
2195 Station Village Way #1407  
San Diego, CA 92104. 

#### 12\. Changes

NewCondosOnline may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your newsletter or other registration or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Any attempt to reproduce or clone the NewCondosOnline.com website is a direct violation of intellectual property rights and will result in legal action against all parties responsible.**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 22, 2005.
